{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge about famous Borises.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who wrote 'War and Peace'?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Leo", "Fyodor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "UK Prime Minister in 2019?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "David", "Theresa"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Russian tennis star?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Andre", "Pete"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Singer of 'Wind of Change'?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Klaus", "James"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Actor in 'GoldenEye'?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Sean", "Pierce"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Boris Godunov?",
      "answers": ["King", "Tsar", "Duke"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Famous chess player?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Garry", "Magnus"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Boris Pasternak?",
      "answers": ["Author", "Singer", "Actor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A character in 'Rocky IV'?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Ivan", "Apollo"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Founder of Boris FX?",
      "answers": ["Tom", "Boris", "John"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Johnson's first name?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Alex", "David"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Russian President in 1991?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Vlad", "Dmitry"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Karloff's fame?",
      "answers": ["Actor", "Writer", "Singer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Becker's sport?",
      "answers": ["Tennis", "Soccer", "Rugby"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Voice actor in 'Toy Story'?",
      "answers": ["Boris", "Tom", "Tim"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Yeltsin's role?",
      "answers": ["PM", "President", "Minister"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Vallejo's art?",
      "answers": ["Sci-Fi", "Fantasy", "Abstract"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Boris Godunov?",
      "answers": ["Poet", "Composer", "Tsar"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Spassky's game?",
      "answers": ["Chess", "Poker", "Golf"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Boris Godunov's opera?",
      "answers": ["Verdi", "Mozart", "Mussorgsky"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
